[

](https://codesteps.com/)

Python, C, C++, C#, PowerShell, Android, Visual C++, Java ...

Search for:  

Search for:  

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective Date: 31-01-2021**

### Your privacy is important to us

It is CodeSteps’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [www.codesteps.com](https://www.codesteps.com/) (hereinafter, “Site”, “us”, “we”, or “www.codesteps.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Site and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of service posted on our Site, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Site. Depending on your activities when visiting our Site, you may be required to agree to additional terms of service.

Contents
--------

Click below to jump to any section of this privacy policy

1. [**Website Visitors**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#websitevisitors)
2. [**Personally-Identifying Information**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#PII)
3. [**Security**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#Security)
4. [**Advertisements**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#Ads)
5. [**Links To External Sites**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#ExternalLinks)
6. [**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#PIIProtection)
7. [**Aggregated Statistics**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#Stats)
8. [**Cookies**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#Cookies)
9. [**Privacy Policy Changes**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#Changes)
10. [**Contact Information & Credit**](https://codesteps.com//privacy-policy/#Credit)

1\. Website Visitors
--------------------

Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. CodeStep’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Site’s visitors use its website. From time to time, CodeSteps may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

CodeSteps also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.codesteps.com blog posts. CodeSteps only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

2\. Personally-Identifying Information
--------------------------------------

Certain visitors to CodeSteps’s websites choose to interact with CodeSteps in ways that require CodeSteps to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that CodeSteps gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who leave a comment at https://www.codesteps.com to provide a username and email address.

3\. Security
------------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

4\. Advertisements
------------------

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by CodeSteps and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

5\. Links To External Sites
---------------------------

Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms of service of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

6\. Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
------------------------------------------------------------

CodeSteps discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on CodeSteps’s behalf or to provide services available at CodeSteps’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using CodeSteps’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. CodeSteps will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, CodeSteps discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when CodeSteps believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of CodeSteps, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of https://www.codesteps.com and have supplied your email address, CodeSteps may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with CodeSteps and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. CodeSteps takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

7\. Aggregated Statistics
-------------------------

CodeSteps may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. CodeSteps may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, CodeSteps does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

8\. Cookies
-----------

To enrich and perfect your online experience, CodeSteps uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. CodeSteps uses cookies to help CodeSteps identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.codesteps.com, and their website access preferences. CodeSteps visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using CodeSteps’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of CodeSteps’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to CodeSteps’s use of cookies.

9\. Privacy Policy Changes
--------------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, CodeSteps may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in CodeSteps’s sole discretion. CodeSteps encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

10\. Contact Information & Credit
---------------------------------

This privacy policy was created at [privacyterms.io privacy policy generator](https://privacyterms.io/privacy-policy-generator/ "Privacy policy generator"). If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via [email](mailto:contact@codesteps.com).

Programming Languages
---------------------

Frameworks
----------

Tags
----

Archives
--------

Archives Select Month July 2023  (1) December 2022  (1) May 2022  (1) April 2022  (1) November 2021  (8) October 2021  (1) August 2021  (1) July 2021  (1) April 2021  (1) October 2020  (1) September 2020  (1) August 2020  (1) May 2020  (3) April 2020  (1) February 2020  (3) January 2020  (2) October 2019  (1) September 2019  (4) August 2019  (11) July 2019  (7) June 2019  (1) May 2019  (4) April 2019  (14) March 2019  (5) February 2019  (9) January 2019  (15) December 2018  (30) November 2018  (30) October 2018  (31) September 2018  (30) August 2018  (31) July 2018  (10) June 2018  (1) May 2018  (1) March 2018  (2) February 2018  (1) January 2018  (3) December 2017  (1) November 2017  (4) October 2017  (2) January 2017  (5) November 2016  (1) June 2016  (1) February 2016  (1) January 2015  (1) December 2014  (1) September 2014  (1) August 2014  (9) July 2014  (25) June 2014  (30) May 2014  (31) April 2014  (30) March 2014  (31) February 2014  (28) January 2014  (31) December 2013  (9) November 2013  (4) October 2013  (5) September 2013  (9) August 2013  (10) July 2013  (10) June 2013  (8) May 2013  (9) April 2013  (4) March 2013  (1) January 2013  (3) June 2012  (1) May 2012  (2) April 2012  (1) March 2012  (6) February 2012  (10) January 2012  (5) December 2011  (5) November 2011  (3) September 2011  (1) August 2011  (2) July 2011  (1) June 2011  (7) May 2011  (9) April 2011  (11)

Meta
----

Follow CodeSteps[

](https://twitter.com/codesteps)[

](https://instagram.com/codestepsblog)

Policies
--------

Copyright © 2024 [CodeSteps](https://codesteps.com/ "CodeSteps"). Powered by [Zakra](https://zakratheme.com/ "Zakra") and [WordPress](https://wordpress.org/ "WordPress").
